# Jonathan Gómez Sánchez

## Full stack web developer

#### **PROFILE**

Full stack developer with more than 1 year working as a web developer specialized in JavaScript and its most popular frameworks. My experience in backend and frontend development allowed me to understand perfectly the comunication in the both sides and also develop skills like solve problems, comunication and teamwork.

#### TOP SKILLS

JavaScript | React JS | Redux | Node JS | Express | PostgreSQL | Css | MySql | PHP | Bootstrap

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Teaching assistant Jan 2023 – Mar 2023 Henry & Remote

Main tasks:

- Guide students in the first steps of the course and clarify their doubts
- Provide assistance in solving exercises and encourage group teamwork (Pair
- Suggest ideas to improve the Bootcamp processes.

#### Internship student in a research seedbed

SENA ∂

• Colaborate developing a platform that can register the ideas and proposals for the "Fondo emprender" program. In that application also people in the program can analyze the proposals, reject or continue with the process.

Web developer Jun 2021 – Jul 2022 Meintegral SAS ≥ Manizales, Colombia

Jun 2022 – Dec 2022

Manizales, Colombia

Achievements:

- Help in the development of a detection of symptoms application in pandemic.
- Colaborate in the production release of a pharmacy inventory application that was implemented in several branches of the company in different departments of the country.

### **EDUCATION**

Full stack web developer	Nov 2022 – Mar 2023
Henry ⊗	Remote
<b>Mechatronic Engineer</b>	Feb 2018 – Dec 2022
Universidad de Caldas ⊘	Manizales, Colombia
Computer equipment technician SENA ⊗	Nov 2020 – Dec 2021 Manizales, Colombia

#### LANGUAGES

#### English

В2